Hi George.
Hi Deb.
Is Nina around?
Nina在吗?
She'll be right back.She's talking to Simon.
她马上就回来. 她在和Simon谈话.
Hm.Do you know her schedule by any chance?
Hm. 你知道她的日程表吗?
Sure.What do you need to know?
当然. 你需要了解什么?
I need to check something on her schedule.
我想核对一下她日程表里的一些情况.
Will she be away at all in the next three weeks?
她之后的三个星期会出差吗?
No,she'll be here.
No, 她会在这儿.
She'll have a few meeting in town,but...
她会去城里参加几个会, 不过...
Nina will travel for business,right?
Nina会出差的, 对吗?
I mean,even though she has Sherise?
我的意思是, 尽管她还有Sherise?
Sure.She just arranges child care with her family.
是的. 她会安排家人照料宝宝.
But she won't go away for long!
但她不会离开很长时间的!
A few days,max.
几天吧, 最多.
Why?What's going on?
Why? 有什么事儿吗?
Anne wants her to go on this next trip.
Anne想让她出下一趟差.
Where?
去哪儿?
Czech Republic.
捷克(Czech)共和国.
Oh man.I'll go.Send me.
Oh man. 我愿意去. 派我去吧.
C'mon Debbie.
Just switch the names on the tickets.No one will ever know.
只要把机票上的名字换换就可以了. 永远不会有人知道的.
No,no.
OK,OK.Don't switch the names.
OK,OK. 不用换名字了.
I'll wear a wig.
我戴个假发.
I'll wear a dress.I'll...Nina!
穿条裙子. 我会...Nina!
Don't ask!
什么都别问!